export const level1 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "12 + 5",
    answer: ['16', '18', '13', '17'],
    true_ans: '17',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "25 + 20",
    answer: ['42', '35', '45', '48'],
    true_ans: '45',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "20+28",
    answer: ['53', '48', '46', '47'],
    true_ans: '48',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "18 + 16",
    answer: ['32', '24', '28', '34'],
    true_ans: '34',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "1 + 56",
    answer: ['56', '66', '57', '51'],
    true_ans: '57',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "25 - 13",
    answer: ['12', '38', '11', '18'],
    true_ans: '12',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "18 / 3",
    answer: ['54', '6', '9', '13'],
    true_ans: '6',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "12 + 26",
    answer: ['33', '49', '38', '51'],
    true_ans: '38',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "33 - 31",
    answer: ['64', '2', '31', '51'],
    true_ans: '2',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "8 * 9",
    answer: ['72', '80', '32', '66'],
    true_ans: '72',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "11 * 11",
    answer: ['101', '91', '121', '81'],
    true_ans: '121',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "66 / 6",
    answer: ['21', '6', '10', '11'],
    true_ans: '11',
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "80 + 8",
    answer: ['91', '88', '84', '100'],
    true_ans: '88',
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "99 - 16",
    answer: ['83', '85', '91', '76'],
    true_ans: '83',
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "87 - 13",
    answer: ['46', '68', '81', '74'],
    true_ans: '74',
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "12 * 13",
    answer: ['136', '166', '156', '96'],
    true_ans: '156',
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "96 / 16",
    answer: ['6', '8', '12', '14'],
    true_ans: '6',
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "89 - 33",
    answer: ['56', '65', '74', '38'],
    true_ans: '56',
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "91 + 9",
    answer: ['99', '100', '120', '92'],
    true_ans: '100',
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "102 - 37",
    answer: ['74', '89', '65', '55'],
    true_ans: '65',
  },
];
